Hi, I'm Chuck Blake. I'm based in Brooklyn, and I've spent my whole career across business,
product, engineering, marketing, operations, all sorts of roles, all at early stage companies.
I'm technical, and I've always been interested in what technology can do to help grow businesses.
And I like messy workflows, business problems. I like figuring out where the real constraints are
and in building something useful around that. I like to take what's working in a system and
make it repeatable so I can run it over and over again. And I've done this from a lot of
different perspectives. I was an operations leader at an early stage startup building AI
infrastructure. I was a technical co-founder. Most recently, I was CTO at a company called
LEA and co-founder, and we were building AI document intelligence for wealth management.
Today, I am doing some work as a fractional CTO at a healthcare startup, and I also build a lot of my
own side projects, including Glance, which we're talking about here today. And I also run a website
that helps independent musicians promote their music. I'm a tinkerer by default, and I've spent
a lot of my time building my tooling, like coding workflows, my agent skills, monitors, reporting
systems. And I really like to treat all that tooling as part of the product. And the interesting
thing, I think, about working with AI tools these days is that a lot of that tinkering really pays
off right away, whereas in the past, it felt like a lot of building reports around your to-do system
or building a knowledge management system. And a lot of times, it didn't have the payoff,
and it felt like you were spending a lot of time tinkering. Now, I feel like that tinkering
really is like you almost see results like right away. And I think that's like very exciting.
And again, like this moment now, especially this year, 2026 has been crazy. I think it's like a
really interesting time for somebody like me. You know, AI gives my mix of business judgment and
technical experience somewhere to play. And I have enough leverage to test like a lot of different
ways of building companies and building products. And that's been a lot of fun. And I like staying
close to the problem. And that's why I like kind of working on a lot of these side projects
and where I can really get in with customers and seeing what their problems are and working with
them.